<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Bunny Blog Blog</title>
        <link>https://blog.astrabun.com/blog</link>
        <description>Bunny Blog Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
            <link>https://blog.astrabun.com/blog/2022/09/19/welcome</link>
            <guid>2022/09/19/welcome</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hello and welcome to my blog!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hello and welcome to my blog!</p><p>I plan on using this space to document projects I'm working on and other longer-form text content that doesn't quite belong on other platforms on which I am a user. </p><p>For the time being, I'm planning on using <a href="https://docusaurus.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Docusaurus</a> to maintain this blog due to its simplicity in setup and authoring. While it may typically be used for documentation purposes, I am a fan of how it handles blogs, so that's the piece I'll be using.</p><p>This blog should also be going live very close to when my main "Linktree-like" website goes live. To find me elsewhere on the web, check out <a href="https://astrabun.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">astrabun.com</a> -- made using React JS + MUIv5. This links hub project was the second time I think I've used TypeScript, which has certainly been interesting so far. Previously, any modern front-end web development I've done has been purely in JavaScript, but from what I've seen in TS so far, I've liked it!</p><p>As a final note on programming/coding/scripting languages, I've definitely got more formal and professional experience with Python, but it is also worth mentioning that most of my knowledge in this space is self-taught. There's always more to learn, and that's exciting! (Also I'm trying to teach myself golang nowadays too).</p><p>Well, until next time!</p><p>&lt;3, Astra</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>